<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TinyTimer</string>
    <string name="toast_message">Hey, you have been using your phone for 30 minutes!</string>
    <string name="is_timer_enabled">is_timer_enabled</string>
    <string name="is_lock_timer_enabled">is_lock_timer_enabled</string>
    <string name="is_message_enabled">is_message_enabled</string>
    <string name="is_animation_enabled">is_animation_enabled</string>
    <string name="selected_animation">selected_animation</string>
    <string name="selected_color_theme">selected_color_theme</string>
    <string name="update_interval">update_interval</string>
    <string name="animation_interval">animation_interval</string>
    <string name="minute_of_message">minute_of_message</string>
    <string name="minute_of_color_change">minute_of_color_change</string>
    <string name="color_theme_AW">Always white/black</string>
    <string name="color_theme_WR">White/black to red</string>
    <string name="color_theme_WY">White/black_to_yellow</string>
    <string name="color_theme_TW">Transparent to white/black</string>
    <string name="color_theme_TR">Transparent to red</string>
    <string name="circling_phases">circling_phases</string>
    <string name="blinking_times">blinking_times</string>
    <string name="icon_corner_radius">icon_corner_radius</string>
    <string name="intro_features">For the last week, you have seen the icon displaying the current session length in minutes. Like this: </string>
    <string name="intro_features_2">In the next week, we will add some attention signals upon the icon, especially when the session length passes a certain threshold, so you will be notified. </string>
    <string name="intro_features_3">We will show you some of the attention signals one by one. You will decide whether and how often you want to receive each signal. </string>
    <string name="intro_features_4">In real phone usage, those signals will only be present after the session length reaches the threshold.</string>
    <string name="color_change">The icon becomes red after the current session reaches the threshold.</string>
    <string name="toast_message_test">The app shows a message after the current session reaches the threshold.</string>
    <string name="animation">The icon has some animations after the current session reaches the threshold.</string>
    <string name="play_sound">The app plays a sound after the current session reaches the threshold.</string>
    <string name="play_vib">The app plays a vibration after the current session reaches the threshold.</string>
    <string name="threshold">The table outlines the percentiles of your phone usage session durations over the last two weeks. </string>
    <string name="review">Please review and confirm. During the next week, you can always come back to change your settings. </string>
    <string name="review_2">Please review and confirm. </string>
    <string name="threshold_in_minute">threshold_in_minute</string>
    <string name="toast_setting">toast_setting</string>
    <string name="animation_setting">animation_setting</string>
    <string name="sound_setting">sound_setting</string>
    <string name="vibration_setting">vibration_setting</string>
    <string name="sound_permission">Please unmute the phone for testing. Doing so will also allow other app to play notification sounds and vibrations. </string>
    <string name="vibration_permission">Please enable vibrations for testing. Doing so will also allow other app to play vibrations. </string>
    <string name="table_desc">Let\'s see some examples about how to set the threshold.</string>
    <string name="table_desc_2_1">For example, approximately 20% of your sessions lasted longer than</string>
    <string name="table_desc_2_2">minutes. If you set the threshold to</string>
    <string name="table_desc_2_3">minutes, about one in five sessions will exceed this duration, at which point you will see those attention signals.</string>
    <string name="table_desc_3_1">Similarly, approximately 10% of your sessions lasted longer than</string>
    <string name="table_desc_3_2">minutes. If you set the threshold to</string>
    <string name="table_desc_3_3">minutes, about one in ten sessions will exceed this duration, at which point you will see those attention signals.</string>
    <string name="table_desc_4">Now, please set your own threshold.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_confirm">This tutorial will take up to 10 minutes. You will experience several attention signals (i.e., color change, toast message, animation, sound, and vibration). Please find some place quiet before starting the tutorial. Are you ready?</string>
    <string name="url_privacy_policy">https://sites.google.com/umd.edu/timer/privacy-policy</string>
    <string name="url_ringer_mode">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o9kYi-yYmmM</string>
    <string name="url_survey1">https://umdsurvey.umd.edu/jfe/form/SV_9M3AzRhuuJkrI22</string>
    <string name="rainbow">Rainbow</string>
    <string name="survey1_instruction">Make sure you are connected to the internet. Click the link below to open the survey in a browser. When you are done, paste the confirmation code and click confirm.</string>
    <string name="instruction_survey2">Reflect on your experience with trying to control your phone usage in the last week, and rate your agreement with the following statements.</string>
    <string name="survey1_completed">survey1_completed</string>
    <string name="survey2_completed">survey2_completed</string>
    <string name="survey3_completed">survey3_completed</string>
    <string name="survey4_completed">survey4_completed</string>
    <string name="tutorial_completed">tutorial_completed</string>
    <string name="day_count">day_count</string>


</resources>